[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "What is the probability now given all the computer projections that you've been looking at, what is the probability today that come Sunday, New York City could get hit by this hurricane in a direct hit?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "probability", "now", "given", "all", "the", "computer", "projections", "that", "you", "'ve", "been", "looking", "at", ",", "what", "is", "the", "probability", "today", "that", "come", "Sunday", ",", "New", "York", "City", "could", "get", "hit", "by", "this", "hurricane", "in", "a", "direct", "hit", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "That is the forecast.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "is", "the", "forecast", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"], "LOCATION": ["New York City"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "Even if it's just a little offshore?", "question_tokens": ["Even", "if", "it", "'s", "just", "a", "little", "offshore", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "RB", "RBR", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Yes, especially if it's a little bit left of the city.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "especially", "if", "it", "'s", "a", "little", "bit", "left", "of", "the", "city", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 24 hours"], "LOCATION": ["Virginia Beach", "Hampton Roads"]}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VB", "CC", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "WRB", "EX", "VBP", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "Are you prepared, do you think, as a state for what may be coming?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "prepared", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "as", "a", "state", "for", "what", "may", "be", "coming", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "Piers, it's been quite a week in the dismal swamp and earthquake and now with this change over the last 24 hours and the storm track looks like it would come right across Virginia Beach and Hampton Roads area where there are 1 million people that will be experiencing hurricane force winds.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "it", "'s", "been", "quite", "a", "week", "in", "the", "dismal", "swamp", "and", "earthquake", "and", "now", "with", "this", "change", "over", "the", "last", "24", "hours", "and", "the", "storm", "track", "looks", "like", "it", "would", "come", "right", "across", "Virginia", "Beach", "and", "Hampton", "Roads", "area", "where", "there", "are", "1", "million", "people", "that", "will", "be", "experiencing", "hurricane", "force", "winds", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "Are you concerned about what may happen if it hits directly on New York City?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "concerned", "about", "what", "may", "happen", "if", "it", "hits", "directly", "on", "New", "York", "City", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "Well, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York City"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "What are you feeling about it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "feeling", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "Don't like this one at all.", "answer_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "like", "this", "one", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "Do you think New York City is ready for this?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "New", "York", "City", "is", "ready", "for", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "Well, New York obviously doesn't get hit by hurricanes very frequently.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "New", "York", "obviously", "does", "n't", "get", "hit", "by", "hurricanes", "very", "frequently", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York City"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 158, "question": "Is that what happens?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "what", "happens", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "WP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 159, "answer": "Absolutely, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "Isn't that leaving it a bit late?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "leaving", "it", "a", "bit", "late", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "Well, evacuation is a very tricky thing, because we've seen instances before -- it's a very expensive proposition.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "evacuation", "is", "a", "very", "tricky", "thing", ",", "because", "we", "'ve", "seen", "instances", "before", "--", "it", "'s", "a", "very", "expensive", "proposition", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gadhafi"]}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "Nic, what's latest over there now?", "question_tokens": ["Nic", ",", "what", "'s", "latest", "over", "there", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "JJS", "IN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "Well, it seems that the rebels were working on rumors rather than fact, places they thought they had Gadhafi surrounded, turned out not to be that.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "seems", "that", "the", "rebels", "were", "working", "on", "rumors", "rather", "than", "fact", ",", "places", "they", "thought", "they", "had", "Gadhafi", "surrounded", ",", "turned", "out", "not", "to", "be", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "So what is your gut feeling about how he may be trying to get out of there, without being spotted, caught or whatever?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "is", "your", "gut", "feeling", "about", "how", "he", "may", "be", "trying", "to", "get", "out", "of", "there", ",", "without", "being", "spotted", ",", "caught", "or", "whatever", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "EX", ",", "IN", "VBG", "VBN", ",", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "This is a smart guy who's incredibly paranoid.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "a", "smart", "guy", "who", "'s", "incredibly", "paranoid", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matthew", "Gadhafi"]}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RBR", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "Do you have any kind of estimate for that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "kind", "of", "estimate", "for", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "You know what's really weird here is, I went over to the Rixos Hotel here, the hotel Matthew and Jomana were held up in by Gadhafi's gunmen, the hotel that we stayed in six weeks earlier on in the year, the government minders who were working with us then, I met one of those at the gate today, this afternoon.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", "'s", "really", "weird", "here", "is", ",", "I", "went", "over", "to", "the", "Rixos", "Hotel", "here", ",", "the", "hotel", "Matthew", "and", "Jomana", "were", "held", "up", "in", "by", "Gadhafi", "'s", "gunmen", ",", "the", "hotel", "that", "we", "stayed", "in", "six", "weeks", "earlier", "on", "in", "the", "year", ",", "the", "government", "minders", "who", "were", "working", "with", "us", "then", ",", "I", "met", "one", "of", "those", "at", "the", "gate", "today", ",", "this", "afternoon", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 271, "question": "Presumably, you'll be dealing with it in your normal fearless way, will you, Jack?", "question_tokens": ["Presumably", ",", "you", "'ll", "be", "dealing", "with", "it", "in", "your", "normal", "fearless", "way", ",", "will", "you", ",", "Jack", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 272, "answer": "I'm not sure.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "Why do you say that about him?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "you", "say", "that", "about", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "What kind of effect can that have on a company that's so s successful?", "question_tokens": ["What", "kind", "of", "effect", "can", "that", "have", "on", "a", "company", "that", "'s", "so", "s", "successful", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "IN", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "Well, of course -- I mean, you never know.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "of", "course", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "you", "never", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "EX", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 340, "question": "What was he like in those days?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "he", "like", "in", "those", "days", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "You know what, he was always interested in every technical electronic gadget there was in the world.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "what", ",", "he", "was", "always", "interested", "in", "every", "technical", "electronic", "gadget", "there", "was", "in", "the", "world", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "Who would be more successful if you hadn't met each other?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "would", "be", "more", "successful", "if", "you", "had", "n't", "met", "each", "other", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "Steve Jobs definitely.", "answer_tokens": ["Steve", "Jobs", "definitely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Apple"]}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "You're still an Apple employee, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'re", "still", "an", "Apple", "employee", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "I'm still an Apple employee.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "still", "an", "Apple", "employee", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Apple"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "NNS", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "How much do you get?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "do", "you", "get", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "I think the check -- I don't even see it, but I think it's a couple hundred bucks every two weeks.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "check", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "even", "see", "it", ",", "but", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "couple", "hundred", "bucks", "every", "two", "weeks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "Do you have any interest in the company?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "interest", "in", "the", "company", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "It should be one dollar1.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "should", "be", "one", "dollar1", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Do you have a stake in the company at all these days?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "a", "stake", "in", "the", "company", "at", "all", "these", "days", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "My wife and I really aren't big stock traders.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "wife", "and", "I", "really", "are", "n't", "big", "stock", "traders", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "What gadgets do you work?", "question_tokens": ["What", "gadgets", "do", "you", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "Oh, my gosh.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "my", "gosh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "Are you an Apple consumer?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "an", "Apple", "consumer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "Number one, I use my computer with the full typing keyboard.", "answer_tokens": ["Number", "one", ",", "I", "use", "my", "computer", "with", "the", "full", "typing", "keyboard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Apple"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "It is an Apple computer?", "question_tokens": ["It", "is", "an", "Apple", "computer", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "Apple, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Apple", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Apple"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "Do you have an iPod?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "an", "iPod", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "I have had non-Apple products many, many times.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "had", "non-Apple", "products", "many", ",", "many", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 407, "question": "What is it about Steve Jobs that made him the genius he became?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "about", "Steve", "Jobs", "that", "made", "him", "the", "genius", "he", "became", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 408, "answer": "His way of thinking -- I call it a higher level.", "answer_tokens": ["His", "way", "of", "thinking", "--", "I", "call", "it", "a", "higher", "level", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Jobs"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "Is that right?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "He's very gracious.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "very", "gracious", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Jobs"]}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", ":", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "Why do they mean so much to you?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "they", "mean", "so", "much", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "You know, it's products -- oh, just like Steve Jobs, I grew up thinking the technology products are the hottest area of the world.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "products", "--", "oh", ",", "just", "like", "Steve", "Jobs", ",", "I", "grew", "up", "thinking", "the", "technology", "products", "are", "the", "hottest", "area", "of", "the", "world", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "RB", ",", "CD", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "What do you think it's going to be going to?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "be", "going", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "Normally I would said, well, 20 years is too far to predict and some very futuristic ideas like computers are going to be conscious and they're going to speak just like you and me.", "answer_tokens": ["Normally", "I", "would", "said", ",", "well", ",", "20", "years", "is", "too", "far", "to", "predict", "and", "some", "very", "futuristic", "ideas", "like", "computers", "are", "going", "to", "be", "conscious", "and", "they", "'re", "going", "to", "speak", "just", "like", "you", "and", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "They won't be able to host shows like this, will they?", "question_tokens": ["They", "wo", "n't", "be", "able", "to", "host", "shows", "like", "this", ",", "will", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "But I don't know if that is going to happen in 20 years.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "that", "is", "going", "to", "happen", "in", "20", "years", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "NNS", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "What is that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "It looks like it to somebody who sees it.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "looks", "like", "it", "to", "somebody", "who", "sees", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "Can you actually tell the time on it?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "actually", "tell", "the", "time", "on", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Have you spoken to Steve since he got sick?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "spoken", "to", "Steve", "since", "he", "got", "sick", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "He's been sick at different stages.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "been", "sick", "at", "different", "stages", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "So you and Kathy are just good friends, yeah?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "and", "Kathy", "are", "just", "good", "friends", ",", "yeah", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "CC", "NNP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "Very good friends.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "good", "friends", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kathy"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RBR", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "Does he have it?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "have", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "It isn't like you are ruthless or you're not ruthless.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "n't", "like", "you", "are", "ruthless", "or", "you", "'re", "not", "ruthless", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NN", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "But in terms of what you know of him, what do you think he'd like the legacy to be, the Steve Jobs legacy to be?", "question_tokens": ["But", "in", "terms", "of", "what", "you", "know", "of", "him", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "he", "'d", "like", "the", "legacy", "to", "be", ",", "the", "Steve", "Jobs", "legacy", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "Giving mankind the most useful, helpful tools we've ever had in our history.", "answer_tokens": ["Giving", "mankind", "the", "most", "useful", ",", "helpful", "tools", "we", "'ve", "ever", "had", "in", "our", "history", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Jobs"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "Was the computer, which you were very instrumental in producing -- is that going to be the greatest invention of the last millennium?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "the", "computer", ",", "which", "you", "were", "very", "instrumental", "in", "producing", "--", "is", "that", "going", "to", "be", "the", "greatest", "invention", "of", "the", "last", "millennium", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "It's hard to say, because a computer used to be a device on its own.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "hard", "to", "say", ",", "because", "a", "computer", "used", "to", "be", "a", "device", "on", "its", "own", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "And they should be out playing konkers and soccer and stuff like that, shouldn't they?", "question_tokens": ["And", "they", "should", "be", "out", "playing", "konkers", "and", "soccer", "and", "stuff", "like", "that", ",", "should", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "VBG", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "I don't think we can stop the effect of the future, the future that we've created giving them devices.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "we", "can", "stop", "the", "effect", "of", "the", "future", ",", "the", "future", "that", "we", "'ve", "created", "giving", "them", "devices", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110825pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 661, "question": "Would you agree with that?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "agree", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]